(Bernadette:)You told her we were
going to get married
(Bernadette:)and she had
a heart attack?
(Howard:)You can't take
that personally.
(Penny:)How else is she supposed
to take it?
(Howard:)What you've got to
(Howard:)keep in mind is that
ever since my dad left,
(Howard:)I've been the whole world
to my mother.
(Howard:)I mean, she'd be
threatened by any woman
(Howard:)who can give me
what she can't.
(Bernadette:)You mean sexual
intercourse?
(Howard:)Well, when you say it like
that you make it sound creepy.
(Penny:)What happened?
(Bernadette:)Howard's mother had
a heart attack
(Bernadette:)because I have
sex with him
(Bernadette:)and she can't.
(Howard:)Bernie, wait!
(Sheldon(to Raj):)I'll give you $1,000
if you'll drive me home.
(Priya:)Nice of you to
come for Howard.
(Penny:)Well, he's my friend.
It's what you do.
(Priya:)I'm sorry, did
I miss something?